

# PERSONAL INFORMATION

I have a year's experience in studying and developing non-commerical projects in JavaScript and its React/Redux libraries. I'm also briefly acquainted with jQuery.

My main aim is to become a highly qualified specialist in the field of commercial projects development.

#### REWARDS AND CERTIFICATES

- First place in the "game design" nomination at the *Ludum Dare* gaming hackathon
- *Udemy* certificate at the end of the paid HTML and CSS course
- Udemy certificate at the end of the paid JavaScript and React/Redux libraries course
- *Udemy* certificate at the end of a paid course of advanced study of JavaScript and the React library
- Imaguru certificate of successful completion of the program of creation of one's own business

# CONTACTS

Phone: +375291919565 Email: shpoisnik@gmail.com Telegram: @shponik

# SOCIAL MEDIA





# **NIKITA SHALIMO**

Frontend developer (Junior)

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

Consulting services for the preparation and performing of course projects on the subject "Computer network hardware"

December 2020 - January 2022

Volunteer at the European Games 2019 in the direction of communication

May 2019 - July 2019

Assistance and consultation for athletes from 50 countries of the world (in English).

#### **EDUCATION**

# Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Bachelor Degree, the Faculty of Computer Systems and Networks, specialty of Computing machines, Systems and Networks" | 2017 -2021.

# PERSONAL QUALITIES

Purposeful, conscientious, hard-working, friendly, responsible, sociable.

# SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/SCSS
- JavaScript/React/Redux
- Webpack/Gulp
- AJAX (Fetch API/XMLHttpRequest/Axios)
- npm
- Git/GitHub
- Scrum
- Windows, Linux, MacOS
- Experience in working with relational databases

### **ENGLISH INTERMEDIATE**

Intermediate level B1

# MY PORTFOLIO

Click me